loltrap.com 2011-10-07

# Privacy Policy – LOL Trap

**LOL Trap Privacy Policy**  
The following privacy statement covers the LOL Trap Website. Please read this statement regarding our websites. If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, pleaseÂ [contact us](http://loltrap.com/contact/ "Contact us").

**Public Forums**  
This site makes chat rooms and message boards available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

**Privacy**

Your privacy on the internet is important to us. As a part of the operation of loltrap.com we gather only email addresses submitted to us, these are used only by ourselves to inform you of any updates or for communication etc and are never passed to any third party for any reason.

The foregoing policy is effective as of January 2009, and loltrap.com reserves the right to change this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. This statement and policies outlined herein are not intended to and do not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party.

**Third Party Advertising**

We use various third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please use the Contact form with any questions.

* Also please be aware that Interest-based advertising will allow advertisers to display ads based on a userâ€™s previous interactions with them, such as visits to advertiser website and also to reach users based on their interests.Â  This policy will go into affect as of April 8, 2009. **Third Party Cookies**

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique â€œcookieâ€ on your browser

**Copyright**

All images on loltrap.com are readily available in various places on the Internet and believed to be in public domain. Images posted are believed to be posted within our rights according to the U.S. Copyright Fair Use Act (title 17, U.S. Code.)

**Claims of Infringement**

If you believe that any content appearing on loltrap.com infringes on your copyright, please let us know. Email contact@loltrap.com  
following information to us and the infringing material will be removed as soon as possible.

(a) your name, address, telephone number, and e-mail address;  
(b) a description of the copyrighted work that you claim has been infringed;  
(c) the exact URL or a description of each place where alleged infringing material is located;  
(d) a statement by you that you have a good faith belief that the disputed use has not been authorized by you, your agent, or the law;  
(e) your electronic or physical signature or the electronic or physical signature of the person authorized to act on your behalf; and  
(f) a statement by you made under penalty of perjury, that the information in your notice is accurate, that you are the copyright owner or authorized to act on the copyright ownerâ€™s behalf

Please also note that under Section 512(f) of the Copyright Act any person who knowingly materially misrepresents that material or activity is infringing may be subject to liability.
